question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In \'Star Trek\', Klingons are commonly referred to as \'Black Elves\'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "An episode of \'The Simpsons\' is dedicated to Moe Szyslak\'s bar rag.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In the animated series Futurama, the character Phllip J. Fry is his own grandfather.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "Bob Ross was a US Air Force pilot.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "Like his character in \'Parks and Recreation\', Aziz Ansari was born in South Carolina.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In \'Star Trek\', Klingons respect William Shakespeare, they even suspect him having a Klingon lineage.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "Klingons once had a period of Democracy in their history, they referred to it as the \'Dark Times\'.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injuried, and helpless.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In the TV series Red Dwarf, Kryten\'s full name is Kryten 2X4B-523P.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In AMC\'s \'The Walking Dead,\' the characters Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced in Season 1.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In \'Star Trek: The Next Generation\', Data is the only android in existence.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "The show \'Gilligan\'s Island\' was cancelled because of low ratings.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "The television show Doctor Who first aired in 1963.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
